<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>configuration on Diwise for Developers</title><link>https://diwise.github.io/tags/configuration/index.html</link><description>Recent content in configuration on Diwise for Developers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://diwise.github.io/tags/configuration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Supported sensor types</title><link>https://diwise.github.io/intro/supported-sensor-types/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://diwise.github.io/intro/supported-sensor-types/index.html</guid><description>Sensor type ID Description qalcosonic Qalcosonic W1 (w1e, w1h, w1t), ultrasonic meter for cold and hot water presence Same as strips_lora_ms_h elsys_codec Use with Elsys ERS sensors enviot tem_lab_14ns SenlabT strips_lora_ms_h Sensative Strips cube02 Sensfarm soil moisture sensor milesight_am100 Milesight AM series sensors qalcosonic Volume (incl. timestamp) Temperature (w1t) - Status (codes &amp;amp; messages) elsys_codec Temperature ExternalTemperature Vdd CO2 Humidity Light Motion Occupancy DigitalInput DigitalInputCounter Depends on the Generic Javascript decoder being installed in the LoRaWAN application server</description></item><item><title>Measurements</title><link>https://diwise.github.io/intro/measurements/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://diwise.github.io/intro/measurements/index.html</guid><description>Measurements are what comes out of a sensor reading. Since sensors don&amp;rsquo;t normally share a common language, diwise will normalize sensor values to OMA LightweightM2M (LwM2M) objects.
Measurement Description AirQuality urn:oma:lwm2m:ext:3428 Conductivity urn:oma:lwm2m:ext:3327 DigitalInput urn:oma:lwm2m:ext:3200 Humidity urn:oma:lwm2m:ext:3304 Illuminance urn:oma:lwm2m:ext:3301 PeopleCount urn:oma:lwm2m:ext:3434 Presence urn:oma:lwm2m:ext:3302 Pressure urn:oma:lwm2m:ext:3323 Temperature urn:oma:lwm2m:ext:3303 Watermeter urn:oma:lwm2m:ext:3424</description></item><item><title>Environments</title><link>https://diwise.github.io/intro/environments/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://diwise.github.io/intro/environments/index.html</guid><description>MVP Warning! This is a feature implementation is an MVP and will be changed in an upcoming PR.
Environment Description It&amp;rsquo;s possible to omit this value air If a sensor is placed within air indoors Indoor sensor lifebuoy Special case, if a presence sensor is used to detect presence of a lifebuoy soil for sensors placed in soil water sensors placed in water Configure Available environments are configured in a iot-device-mgmt configuration file.</description></item><item><title>Add a device</title><link>https://diwise.github.io/getting-started/how-to/add-device/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://diwise.github.io/getting-started/how-to/add-device/index.html</guid><description>Heads up! The device/sensor that should be added need to be of a known type, that is, a decoder for the type of sensor must already exist and the device/sensor should be provisioned within the LoRa application server.
How to add a new sensor Add device metadata Device metadata is stored in iot-device-mgmt. When iot-device-mgmt starts up it load data from csv-files and adds information to its database.
The file 30.</description></item></channel></rss>